Guide to the Printmaker File [1730]-2014, undated (bulk 1800-1860) PR 58
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Prints 16 x 20" to 30 x 40"
  - Cartwright, T.
    - "East View of Baltimore, Maryland", 1802 (Folder FF-C)
      colored aquatint, published by Atkins & Nightingale, London & Philadelphia
  - Cohen, Arthur Allen (b. 1928)
    - Brooklyn Bridge 1 (artist's proof), [1982] (Folder FF-C)
    - Brooklyn Bridge 2 (artist's proof), [1982] (Folder FF-C)
    - Brooklyn Bridge 9 (artist's proof), 1982 (Folder FF-C)
    - Brooklyn Bridge 9 (artist's proof), [1982] (Folder FF-C)
  - Connell, Edwin V.D. (b. 1859)
    - [From the Tower of the Produce Exchange], with remarques of Produce Exchange Tower and Statue of Liberty], 1889 (Folder FF-C)
  - Dawes, D.B. (?)
    - [Village church], undated (Folder FF-D)
  - Doolittle, Amos (1754-1832)
    - "A New Display of the United States", 1803 (Folder FF-D)
      printed and sold by Doolittle, New Haven
  - Doolittle, A. B.
    - "A View of the Buildings of Yale College at New Haven", 1807 (Folder FF-D)
      published by A. Doolittle & Son, New Haven
  - Edy, John William (fl. 1780-1820)
    after George Bulteel Fisher (1764-after 1796).
    - "View of St. Anthony's Nose, on the North River Province of New York", 1795 (Folder FF-E)
      aquatint, published by Edy, Westminster
  - Eisner, Anne (1911-1967), 1940
    Gift, Christie McDonald, January 2022.
    - [Klein's Outer Sanctum], [1940] (Folder FF-E)
      Approximately 23x16 inches.
    - "Klein's Inner Sanctum", 1940 (Folder FF-E)
      Lithograph. Titled, signed, dated (1940), numbered (7/10) by Eisner. With detached label registering the object with the 39th annual water color and print exhibition at the Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts and the Philadelphia Water Color Club (Nov-Dec, 1941). Approximately 18x16 inches.
  - Engelmann, Pére et Fils
    - "Vues de l'Amerique du Nord (1r au 10e le)" [Niagara/Vue de New-York/West Point], [1825-1830] (Folder FF-E)
    - "Vues de l'Amerique du Nord (23me au 32me le)" [Jeux Indiens/Pont de Virginie/Les chutes de Niagara], [1825-1830] (Folder FF-E)
  - Etwiller, ?
    - [Toll Bridge], 1926 (Folder FF-E)
  - Ferguson, Max (b. 1959)
    - [Waiting at the Spring Street Station (55/75), 1985 (Folder FF-F)
  - Fiene, Ernest (1894-1965)
    - Waterfront, Manhattan (3/100), 1931 (Folder FF-F)
    - Waterfront, Manhattan (89/100), 1931 (Folder FF-F)
      Gift of Pam Schaffler
    - New York Skyline (21/40), 1932 (Folder FF-F)
    - New York Skyline (26/40), 1932 (Folder FF-F)
  - Fourdrinier, Paul (fl. 1720-2760)
    after Peter Gordon
    - "A View of Savanah as it stood the 29th of March 1734" (Folder FF-F)
      etching, two copies, both colored
  - Garneray, Ambroise-Louis (1783-1857)
    - "A View of New-York, taken from Veahawk", 1834 (Folder FF-G)
      aquatint by Sigismond Himely, 1801-1872, after a painting by Garneray, Published by Basset, Paris
    - "Vue du Port de Baltimore", [1843-1844] (Folder FF-G)
      aquatint after his own design, published by Hocquart, Paris, and by Bailly, Ward & Co., New York
  - Golinkin, Joseph Webster (1897-1977)
    - Black Window, ca. 1928 (Folder FF-G)
    - [National Horse Show at Madison Square Garden], ca. 1938 (Folder FF-G)
    - [Park Avenue; view south toward New York Central Building] (13/50), [1935] (Folder FF-G)
    - [Speakeasy interior] (7/24), [1928] (Folder FF-G)
  - Graham, George (fl. 1786-1813)
    after Archibald Robertson (1765-1835).
    - "A View on Hudson River, taken from the farm of Mr. James Renwick upon Chambers Creek near Newburgh", 1795 (Folder FF-G)
      mezzotint stipple engraving, published by James Harrison, New York
  - Grooms, Red (b. 1937) (Box-folder .)
    - Lunchtime on Broadway, 2009 (Folder FF-G)
      Etching with aquatint, spitbite aquatint and scrapping
  - Hagopian, Vahan (b. 1889)
    - [51st St. and Park Ave., showing St. Bartholmew's Church], undated (Box Unknown container 866 for instance of [51st St. and Park Ave., showing St. Bartholmew's Church], Folder unknown container)
    - Martin Beck Theatre, undated (Box Unknown container 867 for instance of Martin Beck Theatre, Folder unknown container)
      lithograph, 2 copies
    - [Street Corner in Midtown] (Box Unknown container 868 for instance of [Street Corner in Midtown], Folder unknown container)
  - Hall, John (1739-1797)
    after Benjamin West (1738-1820).
    - "William Penn's Treaty with the Indians, when he founded the province of Pennsylvania in North America, 1681", 1775 (Box Unknown container 869 for instance of "William Penn's Treaty with the Indians, when he founded the province of Pennsylvania in North America, 1681", Folder unknown container)
      engraving, published by John Boydell, London, two copies, one colored
  - Hass, Richard (b. 1936)
    - "View of Woolworth Building from World Trade Center" (30/75), undated (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
    - "Manhattan View, Twilight", 1999 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
      Studio proof
  - Hauben, Daniel (b. 1956)
    - Evening Rain (46/50), 1998 (Box Unknown container 870 for instance of Evening Rain (46/50), Folder unknown container)
    - Fire Escapes (17/35), 1983 (Box Unknown container 871 for instance of Fire Escapes (17/35), Folder unknown container)
      serigraph
  - Hios, Theo (1908-1999)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Workers, 1937 (Box Unknown container 872 for instance of Brooklyn Bridge Workers, Folder unknown container)
    - War Victim, 1938 (Box Unknown container 873 for instance of War Victim, Folder unknown container)
  - Hirschfeld, Al (1903-2003)
    - "1776", 1997 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
      Brent Spinner, Pat Hingle, Paul Michael Valley, designed by Tony Walton, 1997, AP #VII/XV. Lithograph 20 x 24 in.
    - "A&E Biography (TV)", 1997 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
      Lithograph 20 x24 in. Historic figures Pres. Ronald Reagan, Gov. Nelson Rockefeller, Marilyn Monroe, Leonardo da Vinci, Mohammad Ali, General George Patton, F. Scott Fitzgerald, Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis, AP #V/XL
    - "Josephine Baker", 2002 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
      lithograph, ink and watercolor, 20 x 24, AP #7/40
    - "Cultural Calendar", 1984 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
      lithograph, 20 x 24 in., Mehta, Bernstein, Tandy, Landsbury, AP #XIII/XXXVIII
    - [Barbara Streisand], undated (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
  - Hulett, James (d. 1771)
    after Nicholas Garrison.
    - "A View of the House of Employment, Alms-House, Pennsylvania Hospital, & part of the City of Philadelphia", 1787 (Box Unknown container 874 for instance of "A View of the House of Employment, Alms-House, Pennsylvania Hospital, & part of the City of Philadelphia", Folder unknown container)
      engraving, published by J. Harris, New York, State II
  - Hung, Su-Li (b. 1947)
    - Broken City (6/50), 2001 (Box Unknown container 875 for instance of Broken City (6/50), Folder unknown container)
    - World Trade Center (2/50), 2001 (Box Unknown container 876 for instance of World Trade Center (2/50), Folder unknown container)
  - Hunter, F[rederick] Leo (1862-1943)
    - Coenties Slip, South Street, 1881 (Box Unknown container 877 for instance of Coenties Slip, South Street, Folder unknown container)
    - N.Y. Produce Exchange, 1887 (Box Unknown container 878 for instance of N.Y. Produce Exchange, Folder unknown container)
  - Jefferys, Thomas
    After George Heap.
    - "An East Prospect of the City of Philadelphia taken by George Heap from the Jersey Shore", [1756] (Box Unknown container 879 for instance of "An East Prospect of the City of Philadelphia taken by George Heap from the Jersey Shore", Folder unknown container)
      engraving, published by Jefferys, London
  - Johnston, Thomas (1708-1767)
    - "A Prospective Plan of the Battle Fought near Lake George on the 8th of Sept. 1755..." (Box Unknown container 880 for instance of "A Prospective Plan of the Battle Fought near Lake George on the 8th of Sept. 1755...", Folder unknown container)
      after S. Blodget
  - Jukes, Francis (1745-1812)
    after Alexander Robertson (1772-1841).
    - "Hudsons River from Chambers Creek looking thro' the High Lands", 1802 (Box Unknown container 881 for instance of "Hudsons River from Chambers Creek looking thro' the High Lands", Folder unknown container)
      colored aquatint, published by Jukes, London, and Robertson, New York
    - "New York from Hobuck Ferry House New Jersey", 1800 (Box Unknown container 882 for instance of "New York from Hobuck Ferry House New Jersey", Folder unknown container)
    - "Mount Vernon in Virginia the Seat of the late Lieut. General George Washington Commander in Chief of the Armies of the United States", 1800 (Box Unknown container 883 for instance of "Mount Vernon in Virginia the Seat of the late Lieut. General George Washington Commander in Chief of the Armies of the United States", Folder unknown container)
  - Katz, Steven
    - 57th Street Bridge, 2013 (Box FF, Folder unknown container)
      General
      Etching
    - Ansonia 1, 2013 (Box FF, Folder unknown container)
    - Comfort Inn, 2014 (Box FF, Folder unknown container)
  - Klein, Sabina
    - Chelsea Afternoon, undated (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
  - Le Breton, Louis (1818-1866)
    - "Vue de New York Arrivee du transatlantique", 1820 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
  - Levi, Julian E. (1900-1982), circa 1970
    - [Statue of Liberty], circa 1970 (Folder FF)
      Lithograph. Artists proof. Signed by artist. Unframed by N-YHS conservator Kate Bator in December 2019. A photocopy of a 1975 letter from the artist to Saul Wolf is included in the folder; this has his comments about the subject matter and imagery (i.e., decapitated Statue of Liberty, caged doves of peace), the context of creation (in Paris, during the Vietnam War), and number of prints made (50).
      Gift, Jessica Wolf, 2016. Credit line: Donated by Jessica Wolf, Stratford, CT in memory of her parents Anne and Saul Wolf of East Hampton, NY
  - Mackay, Donald A.
    - Farewell to the Hotel Astor (35/100), undated (Box Unknown container 884 for instance of Farewell to the Hotel Astor (35/100), Folder unknown container)
  - McKenzie, Mary Beth (b. 1946)
    - "Readings by Miss Lil", 2002 (Folder FF McKenzie 1)
      monotype, 11 1/4" x 14"
    - "Fulton Fish Market", 2002 (Folder FF McKenzie 1)
      monotype, 12" x 13 1/4"
    - Untitled, 1999 (Folder FF McKenzie 1)
      monotype, sheet: 12 ½" x 15 9/16"
    - "The Bakery Interior", 1998 (Folder FF McKenzie 1)
      monotype, 14 7/8" x 12 7/8"
    - Untitled, Circus series, 2013 (Folder FF McKenzie 1)
      monotype, 13 5/8" x 16 ½"
    - "Men at Tire Shop on West 45th Street", 2013 (Folder FF McKenzie 1)
      monotype, sheet: 14 1/8 x 21"
    - "New York City Horse and Carriage Barn", ca. 1980 (Folder FF McKenzie 1)
      monotype, sheet: 12 5/8" x 15 7/8"
    - [Win Big Prizes], Coney Island series, 2017 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
      Monotype.
    - [Roller Coaster and Concessions], Coney Island series, 2018 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
    - [Nathan's World Famous Frankfurters], Coney Island series, 2018 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
    - [Steeplechase Funny Face Over Entry Gate], Coney Island series, 2015 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
    - [Nathan's Hot Dog Eating Contest], Coney Island series, 2019 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
    - [Parachute Jump with Sandy Beach], Coney Island series, 2018 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
    - [Nathan's with Outdoor Seating], Coney Island series, 2017 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
    - [Carousel], Coney Island series, 2013 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
    - [Performing for a Crowd], Coney Island series, 2017 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
    - [Parachute Jump, blue background], Coney Island series, 2018 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
    - [Posing Under Mermaid Sign], Coney Island series, 2019 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
    - [Snake Child], Coney Island series, 2019 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
    - [Wonder Wheel], Coney Island series, 2017 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
    - [Bathers in the Ocean], Coney Island series, 2018 (Folder FF McKenzie 2)
  - Mielatz, Charles Frederick William (1864-1919)
    - The Dewey Arch, 1900 (Folder FF Mielatz)
  - New York Etcher's Press
    - "A Day in Times Square", 2009 (Box Flat files, Folder 1)
      Porfolio of nine prints featuring un-edited artist reflectings about Times Square: Arisman, Marshall, "The Dancing Bear" (etching); Chernow, Ann, "Victory Theatre, 1942" (photo-etching); Hardin, Maya, untitled (4-plate, 4-color aquatint); Lasansky, Richie, untitled (engraving, etching, scraped, aquatint, drypoint); Netter, Lou, "Broken Bodies Broken Wallets" (etching, aquatint); Ronalds, Bill, "X-Termination" (aquatint); Waldman, Bruce, untitled (litho crayon open bite).
  - Pantell, Richard (b. 1927)
    - The Five Points, 1985 (Box Unknown container 886 for instance of The Five Points, Folder unknown container)
  - Pelletieri, Michael (b. 1947)
    - City Signs, 2003 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
  - Pennell, Joseph (1860-1926)
    - "The Cut Toward Culebra", 1912 (Box Unknown container 887 for instance of "The Cut Toward Culebra", Folder unknown container)
  - Penney, James (1910-1982)
    - Subway (3/10), 1932 (Box Unknown container 888 for instance of Subway (3/10), Folder unknown container)
  - Podwal, Mark (b. 1945)
    - "Ship of State", 2002 (Box Unknown container 889 for instance of "Ship of State", Folder unknown container)
      etching, impression 13 of 60
  - Robinson, Boardman (1856-1952)
    - [Walt Whitman], undated (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
  - Rollinson, William (1762-1842)
    after John Wood (b. 1775)
    - "New York from Long Island", 1801 (Box Unknown container 890 for instance of "New York from Long Island", Folder unknown container)
      aquatint, published by Wood and Rollinson, New York
  - Rowland, Susan
    - "Trinity Graveyard, May 7, 2002" (Box FF, Folder unknown container)
      Monoprint with weed, 8 x 22 in., signed SR 1/1. Gift of Kate Ganz, 2003.
  - Sakuyama, Shunji
    - [100 Garfield Place, Brooklyn], 1982 (Box Unknown container 891 for instance of [100 Garfield Place, Brooklyn], Folder unknown container)
      color lithograph, monoprint
    - [465 Fourteenth Street, Brooklyn] (18/26), 1981 (Box Unknown container 892 for instance of [465 Fourteenth Street, Brooklyn] (18/26), Folder unknown container)
      color lithograph
    - [558 Second Street, Brooklyn] (12/18), 1983 (Box Unknown container 893 for instance of [558 Second Street, Brooklyn] (12/18), Folder unknown container)
    - [Room interior] (14/23), 1982 (Box Unknown container 894 for instance of [Room interior] (14/23), Folder unknown container)
  - Sanchez, Emilio (1921-1999)
    - Crosstown Sunset, color lithograph (47/75), 1976 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
    - Crosstown Traffic, color lithograph (4/100), 1998 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
    - Hudson River View, color lithograph (8/50), 1980's (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
    - Loft Windows, color lithograph (42/100), 1988 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
    - Looking West from My Studio, color lithograph (16/100), 1988 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
    - New York on a Sunny Day, color lithograph (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
    - Nueva York, color lithograph (32/75), ca 1977 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
    - The Shadow of the Brooklyn Bridge, color lithograph, (32/100), 1988 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
    - The View from New York, color lithograph, (1/75), 1976 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
  - Sandby, Paul (1731-1809)
    after sketches by Thomas Pownall.
    - Title page, "Six Remarkable Views in the Provinces of New-York, New-Jersey, and Pennsylvania, in North America", 1761 (Box Unknown container 895 for instance of Title page, "Six Remarkable Views in the Provinces of New-York, New-Jersey, and Pennsylvania, in North America", Folder unknown container)
      printed by Thomas Jefferys, London [includes list of 6 plates]
    - "A View in Hudson's River of the Entrance of What is called the Topan Sea", 1761 (Box Unknown container 896 for instance of "A View in Hudson's River of the Entrance of What is called the Topan Sea", Folder unknown container)
      painted by Sandby, engraved by Peter Benazech, published by Thomas Jefferys, London. Additional copy of a later issue, colored.
    - "A View of the Falls on the Passaick, or Second River, in the Province of New Jersey", 1761 (Box Unknown container 897 for instance of "A View of the Falls on the Passaick, or Second River, in the Province of New Jersey", Folder unknown container)
      painted and engraved by Sandby, published by Thomas Jefferys, London. Additional copy of a later issue.
    - "A View in Hudson's River of Pakepsey & the Catts-Kill Mountain, from Sopos Island in Hudson's River", 1761 (Box Unknown container 898 for instance of "A View in Hudson's River of Pakepsey & the Catts-Kill Mountain, from Sopos Island in Hudson's River", Folder unknown container)
    - "A View of the Great Cohoes Falls on the Mohawk River", 1761 (Box Unknown container 899 for instance of "A View of the Great Cohoes Falls on the Mohawk River", Folder unknown container)
      painted by Sandby, engraved by William Elliot, published by Thomas Jefferys, London. Two additional copies of a later issue.
    - "A View of Bethlem, the Great Moravian Settlement in the Province of Pennsylvania", 1761 (Box Unknown container 900 for instance of "A View of Bethlem, the Great Moravian Settlement in the Province of Pennsylvania", Folder unknown container)
      painted and engraved by Sandby, published by Thomas Jefferys, London.
    - "A Design to Represent the Beginning and Completion of an American Settlement or Farm", 1761 (Box Unknown container 901 for instance of "A Design to Represent the Beginning and Completion of an American Settlement or Farm", Folder unknown container)
      painted by Sandby, engraved by James Peake, published by Thomas Jefferys, London. Two copies, one additional copy of a later issue.
  - Schwartz, Peri (b. 1951)
    - "Woman on subway" (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
      artist's proof
    - "Subway" (2/25), 1977 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
    - "Grand Army Plaza I" (1/1), 1979 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
    - "Reading Room II" (1/1), 1976 (Box Flat files, Folder unknown container)
  - Scott, Dread (b. 1965)
    - "Triangle Shirt Waste", 2001 (Box FF, Folder unknown container)
      Sceen print on paper, 7/14
    - "We are the 99%", 2011 (Box FF, Folder unknown container)
      Screen print on paper, 2/7
    - "We are the 99%-Arabic", 2011 (Box FF, Folder unknown container)
    - "Eimazte to 99%", 2011 (Box FF, Folder unknown container)
    - "Somos El 99%", 2011 (Box FF, Folder unknown container)
      Screen print on paper 2/7
    - "Siamo Il 99%", 2011 (Box FF, Folder unknown container)
  - Seymour, Samuel (fl. 1797-1823)
    after William Birch (1755-1834).
    - "The City of New York in the State of New York North America", 1803 (Box Unknown container 902 for instance of "The City of New York in the State of New York North America", Folder unknown container)
      engraving, published by William Birch, Pennsylvania. One copy of first state, colored, and one copy of third state [with added picnickers and William Morgan's imprint, ca. 1820], uncolored
  - Simon, Tavik Frantisek (1877-1942)
    - [Broad Street with New York Stock Exchange], 1927 (Box Unknown container 903 for instance of [Broad Street with New York Stock Exchange], Folder unknown container)
      color aquatint
    - [Broadway at night], [1927] (Box Unknown container 904 for instance of [Broadway at night], Folder unknown container)
    - [New York Public Library in winter], 1927 (Box Unknown container 905 for instance of [New York Public Library in winter], Folder unknown container)
    - [View of Lower Manhattan from Brooklyn Bridge walkway at dusk], [1927] (Box Unknown container 906 for instance of [View of Lower Manhattan from Brooklyn Bridge walkway at dusk], Folder unknown container)
  - Sloat, Richard Joel (b. 1945)
    - Not So Flat Iron(2/50), 1996 (Box Unknown container 907 for instance of Not So Flat Iron(2/50), Folder unknown container)
      woodblock print
    - Rising Sun (35/90), 1977 (Box Unknown container 908 for instance of Rising Sun (35/90), Folder unknown container)
    - Walk Down St. Marks (5/90), 1994 (Box Unknown container 909 for instance of Walk Down St. Marks (5/90), Folder unknown container)
  - Smillie, James (1807-1885)
    after Thomas Cole (1801-1848).
    - "Voyage of Life, Childhood", undated (Box Unknown container 910 for instance of "Voyage of Life, Childhood", Folder unknown container)
      proof with no publisher listed, printed by H. Peters
    - "Voyage of Life, Youth", undated (Box Unknown container 911 for instance of "Voyage of Life, Youth", Folder unknown container)
      printed by J. Dalton
    - "Voyage of Life, Manhood", undated (Box Unknown container 912 for instance of "Voyage of Life, Manhood", Folder unknown container)
    - "Voyage of Life, Old Age", undated (Box Unknown container 913 for instance of "Voyage of Life, Old Age", Folder unknown container)
  - Smith, Samuel
    after Thomas Leitch (fl. 1771).
    - "A View of Charles-Town, the Capitol of South Carolina", 1776 (Box Unknown container 914 for instance of "A View of Charles-Town, the Capitol of South Carolina", Folder unknown container)
      published by Smith, London
  - Soyer, Raphael (1899-1987)
    - Immigrants, 1969 (Box-folder .)
      Lithograph. Source of Acquisition: Gift of Mr. & Mrs. Lawrence Appel, April 2016.
  - Stadler, Joseph Constantine (fl. 1780-1812)
    after William Roberts (1788-1867).
    - "The Natural Bridge", 1808 (Box Unknown container 915 for instance of "The Natural Bridge", Folder unknown container)
      colored aquatint, published in London
  - Strickland, William (1788-1854)
    - "Monumental Church at Richmond", [1810] (Box Unknown container 916 for instance of "Monumental Church at Richmond", Folder unknown container)
      perspective and engraving by Strickland, aquatinted by William Kneass, published by William Kneass
    - "View of the Water Gap and Columbia Glassworks--River Delaware", [1815-1818] (Box Unknown container 917 for instance of "View of the Water Gap and Columbia Glassworks--River Delaware", Folder unknown container)
      aquatint after Thomas Birch, 1779-1851. Two copies, one colored.
  - Tiebout, Cornelius (ca. 1777-ca. 1830)
    - "A View of Rensselaerville Manufactory The Property of Mr. James Caldwell, of the City of Albany, Merchant, with a Distant Prospect of Hudsons River and the Seat of Stephen Van Rensselaer Esquire", 1792 (Box Unknown container 918 for instance of "A View of Rensselaerville Manufactory The Property of Mr. James Caldwell, of the City of Albany, Merchant, with a Distant Prospect of Hudsons River and the Seat of Stephen Van Rensselaer Esquire", Folder unknown container)
    - "Loss of the Packet Ship Albion", undated (Box Unknown container 919 for instance of "Loss of the Packet Ship Albion", Folder unknown container)
      after Thomas Birch, 1779-1851, printed by William H. Morgan, Philadelphia. Two copies.
    - "View in Noble Borough State of New York", undated (Box Unknown container 920 for instance of "View in Noble Borough State of New York", Folder unknown container)
  - Trueblood, Emily (b. 1942)
    - City Towers (2/50), 1994 (Box Unknown container 921 for instance of City Towers (2/50), Folder unknown container)
    - Night Tower (31/50), 2000 (Box Unknown container 922 for instance of Night Tower (31/50), Folder unknown container)
  - Varian, George (1865-1923)